# **Evan Cornish**

#### student

egcornish@gmail.com

## Summary

I was a piano teacher and musician for 3 years before embarking on a career in gambling professionally. As my gambling career started to wind down I've found a passion in technology and hope to work in artificial intelligence at some point.

## Experience

#### Professional gambler at N/A - Currently Self Employed

March 2009 - July 2014 (5 years 5 months)

I played poker professionally as well as sports betting. I built many tools using excel and python including a model that solved a diluted version of the game Pot Limit Omaha

#### Piano Teacher at Self-Employeed

January 2006 - March 2008 (2 years 3 months)

I taught piano lessons to kids ages 6-24.

## Education

### The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science, 2016 - 2020

Grade: Sophomore

Activities and Societies: Chess Club

#### Free Code Camp

Full Stack Web Development Certification, Computer Software Engineering, 2016 - 2017

## Languages

English (Native or bilingual proficiency)
Thai (Professional working proficiency)

**Spanish** (Elementary proficiency)

# **Evan Cornish**

## student

egcornish@gmail.com



Contact Evan on LinkedIn